http://www.azcentralcu.org/privacy-policy

FACTS
WHAT DOES ARIZONA CENTRAL CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
- Social Security number and account balances
- account transactions and credit history
- employment information and transaction or loss history
How?
All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information; the reasons Arizona Central Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Arizona Central Credit Union share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes -
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or to report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes -
to offer our products and services to you
Yes
Yes
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
Yes
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes - information about your transactions and experiences
No
We don't share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
No
We don't share
For nonaffiliates to market to you
No
We don't share
To limit our sharing
- Call toll-free 1-866-264-6421
If you are a new member, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?
Call toll-free 1-866-264-6421 or go to www.azcentralcu.org
What we do
How does Arizona Central Credit Union protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. Access to nonpublic personal information is restricted to employees who need it to serve you. We maintain physical, electronic, or procedural safeguards complying with federal regulations to guard your information.
How does Arizona Central Credit Union collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
- open an account or apply for a loan
- use your credit or debit card or give us your employment information
- make deposits or withdrawals from your account
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
- sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
- affiliates from using your information to market to you
- sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?
Your choices will apply to everyone on your account – unless you tell us otherwise
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
- Arizona Central Credit Union has no affiliates
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
- Nonaffiliates we share with can include insurance companies, government agencies, plastic card processors (credit/debit/ATM), financial statement publishers or printers, mailhouse, mortgage service companies, consumer reporting agencies, data processors, and check/share draft printers
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include CUNA Mutual Group's MEMBERCONNECT and loan recapture programs
×
Affiliate Site Disclaimer
By accessing the noted link, you will be leaving our website and entering an affiliate site, which is hosted by another party. Please be advised that you will no longer be subject to, or under the protection of, the privacy and security policies of our website. We encourage you to read and evaluate the privacy and security policies of the site, which you are entering, which may be different from those of ours.
Close
Continue
Continue
Continue
×
Affiliate Site Disclaimer
By accessing the noted link, you will be leaving our website and entering an affiliate site, which is hosted by another party. Please be advised that you will no longer be subject to, or under the protection of, the privacy and security policies of our website. We encourage you to read and evaluate the privacy and security policies of the site, which you are entering, which may be different from those of ours.
Close
Continue
